Slip of a girl
You play the character
We'll be right back.
Crazed cry of thunder death.
Miss Kunroti!
Love breathing.
Third form.
Cat love shower!
You might look like a kid, but that doesn't mean that I'm going to hold back!
Oh my!
This young girl somehow managed to slash through my attack.
I've never seen a sword like that.
It's too fast for my eyes to follow it.
Is it because of its unique shape?
I can't believe how flexible it is!
Her swordsmith is amazing, but she's even more amazing for being able to wield it!
Love breathing!
Second form!
Love wings!
Six form!
Catlegs wins a bluff!
If she can keep up with this speed, then I'll bury her with a spell!
Blood demon art!
Countless striking trees!
What a widespread attack!
Oh no!
The main body!
Can I take on this many of them at once?
Love breathing!
Fifth form!
Swaying love!
Wild draw!
Got it!
She's fast, but still!
Miss Conroji!
Is he about to attack?
As long as I decapitate him, I'll be okay!
Miss Conroji!
That's not the main body!
It won't die if you behead it!
What?
Seriously?
I heard I made the wrong call!
Compress sound waves!
Miss Conroji!
This girl, even after being attacked, managed to keep her body structure unbroken.
Is it because she tensed up all her muscles just before getting hit?
Even so, she shouldn't have been able to survive that attack.
Inconceivable!
Wait, I see.
This girl's slender physique belies her true muscle density.
An abnormal constitution.
This is good.
Consuming high-quality flesh leads directly to gaining strength.
But before I devour her, I'll pulverize her skull and brain tissue to a pulp.
Ms. Conroji?
No person would ever marry you, but if you're lucky, a bear, boar, or cow might.
Your unnatural hair color is bizarre.
The idea of passing it to my children makes me shudder.
I cannot arrange a marriage with you.
Please forget that you ever met me.
Goodbye.
At 17, my prospective marriage was called off.
Your daddy's amazing, isn't he?
Are you really showing off in front of our child?
My arms were so thin that I wasn't able to flex them.
But there's a story that my mother used to tell me over and over again about my childhood.
When I was just 14 months old.
Right around the time when my mother was pregnant with my little brother.
Mitsuri?
Mitsuri, where are you?
Mits?
Even though I was still just a child, I wanted to help her in the kitchen.
So I somehow went and lifted a 33-pound pickling stone.
Though my mother was known for being unfazed by everything.
That day, for the first time in her life, she found herself blown away.
Thanks for always being a good little helper.
And, ever since I was a child, I've had a pretty big appetite.
I simply love to eat.
Now, that's how it's done!
Come on!
Can't you sumo wrestlers eat that much?
It's not that we can't, it's just...
Well...
There you go.
Sakura Rice Cakes for dessert.
Thank you!
Are you really sure about this?
It's totally fine.
There's no need for you to hold back at all.
Well, you heard the man, right?
So no excuses!
Ready, and...
Go!
Your arms may be thin, Mitsuri.
But the density of your muscles is downright extraordinary!
But, as I grew older, little by little, I began to realize that I wasn't like the other girls around me.
Hey, Mother, do you think I'll ever become someone's bride?
Why would you ask something like that?
You know, because I'm so strong, and I eat all the time, and my hair color is so weird.
You know you're more than welcome to stay at home forever, Mitsuri.
But, Dad, aren't women supposed to get married and become someone's mother?
Sure, but you could also just stay at home.
The day my prospective marriage was called off, I decided I had to hide it all.
So I dyed my hair black.
I stifled my urge to eat.
And I pretended to be weak.
Everyone in my family worried about me.
Soon after, a day came where I met a man who said he wanted to marry me.
Should I do this?
Should I let this happen?
Am I going to live like this for the rest of my life?
Eating voraciously?
Being strong?
My hair color?
All of that is who I am.
Should I pretend to be someone I'm not?
Isn't there something else I can do?
Some way that I can help others while still being me?
Or does this mean that there's no place in this world for me as I am?
Isn't there anyone out there who will love me for being me?
No, this isn't right.
It can't be.
Get up, get up, get up.
The next attack's coming.
I know that, alright.
Huh?
Did I just pass out?
Protect Ms. Konroji!
Ms. Konroji's our only ray of hope.
She's the most skilled.
As long as she survives, there's still a chance to win.
We can do this!
No one has to die!
We can do it!
Your struggling is comical.
You're kidding!
Did I get them?
Thank you, guys!
Forgive me!
I'm a Hashira, but I messed up!
I swear I'll always protect my comrades!
Because the Demon Slayer Corps and its members are my home!
I don't care if you're an upper rank or whatever!
Incredible!
She slashed through it all!
As if I'd ever lose to a jerk like you!
You better brace yourself!
Because I'm going all out!
This is splendid.
It appears the gods smiled upon you when they bestowed their gifts.
Mitsuri.
Take pride in the strength you have.
All those who speak out against you merely fear your talents and envy you for what they haven't.
Thank you so much!
Father, mother, thank you for making me strong from birth.
Everyone in the Demon Slayer Corps has accepted me for who I am.
Promoted to Hashira, congratulations!
Congratulations!
Thanks, you guys!
I'll do my best!
You guys want some?
There's Sakura Rice Cakes!
When I saved people from demons, they would always thank me with tears streaming down their faces.
That's a Hashira for ya!
In one strike!
That evil demon's not gonna hurt you!
You're safe now!
I promise!
From the bottom of our hearts, thank you!
Thank you, miss!
It was Mr. Igaro who gave me the long striped socks I always wear.
Here.
What?
What's this?
Mr. Igaro, what's this?
Take them.
Huh?
Really for me?
Thank you!
I promise you I'll treasure them!
There's no need to treasure them.
Huh?
Oh, no way!
That would be such a waste.
It's fine.
If they get ripped, then I'll give you a new pair.
Huh?
I've often found myself thinking things like, should a girl be this strong?
Would people start saying yet again that I couldn't be human if I were?
I've been so afraid that I've been holding back my power.
But I'm through with that.
Ms. Tanrochi's our only ray of hope!
Huh?
Just leave it to me.
I'll protect you all no matter what!
I'll take care of this one by myself!
You guys go on ahead!
Defeat the main body!
Nezuko!
Genya!
I've got to increase my heart rate!
I need to speed up my circulation!
Move faster!
Get stronger!
More!
You little brats!
Huh?
If you want to get to my comrades, then you're going to have to get through me!
Tanjiro!
Where's the thing with the main body?
Can you track it?
I'll try!
Found it!
This way!
Miss Konrochi can only hold off that child demon for so long!
We have to slash the main body before it's too late!
This young girl, she's moving even faster than before!
I don't understand.
What's happening?
How was she?
Oh, I don't know, it's too late!
I don't know who's room for another class in here?
I'm so tired!
Exactly, isn't it?
Right now?
I feel recursos!
floats but water!
I hope you're going to have to go here!
Why?
Well, it need to get through this?
No!
What?
Belgian?
This is beyond annoying. Thanks to the slip of a girl, I can't unleash my dragons on those brats.
Despicable. Nevertheless, it won't last forever. She'll run out of stamina eventually. The way all humans do.
I will protect them, no matter the cost!
There! It's inside that tree! I'm positive. The demon is hiding inside of it! Hurry!
Almost there! Get out of there, you bastards!
Don't let it shake you off! Hang on! Hang on! We have to strike it down! Before that snake dragon thing starts heading this way! While Ms. Konroji's stopping it from attacking!
I can't swing my sword while holding on! But I can still do this!
Whoa! He's fighting it! His teeth are crazy strong! But won't that upset your stomach? Danya, are you gonna be okay?
If I devour demons, it's only temporary. But I can gain demonic traits!
If I consume a strong demon, it boosts my regenerative abilities and increases my muscular strength!
It's down! Now!
The branches are like whips! Stand your ground! Keep moving!
Nasuko's blood demon heart! Thanks to the flames, it's sluggish now! This will work! I can do this!
Kino Kamikagura! Flame dance!
I still haven't landed a hit!
This won't end until I behead the main body!
Tadjiro! Do it!
It's gone! It must have run off again! But where?
It can't have gotten that far!
Bastard! Get back here!
You can't run away from your sins!
Every atrocity you've committed! Every evil deed!
I'm going to make you pay for everything you've ever done!
You're not escaping me!
No one else can take responsibility for what you've done!
No one else can take responsibility for what you've done! It has to be you and you alone!
You no good, two-faced, shameless liar!
Ever since the day I was born into this accursed world, I've never once uttered a lie!
I'm a virtuous weakling!
As pitiful as I am, nobody shows me any sympathy!
I...
I've never told a lie!
Now...
...
I'm putting an end to this you stubborn
I've always been looking for life
I've never been looking for love
I've never been to the end of this night
I've never been to the end of this
My life is so good
Oh
Miss Konroji, thank you for protecting all of us
You have my word, we'll defeat that demon
Now it's time for a taisho era secret
Get a load of this, eating 170 sakura rice cakes every day for eight months
Cost Miss Konroji's hair and eyes to change their color
Wow, is that true?
This is Miss Konroji we're talking about
I don't know, I feel like it's impossible to eat that many sakura rice cakes without me
Here, for you, Muichiro
Miss Konroji
Why don't you take one for yourself, Tanjiro?
Thank you very much
These are really good
Next the final episode, a connected bond, daybreak and first light
No way are we gonna let some arrogant demon have his way
That's right
Let's give our all
No way we're gonna lose